Guide to the Andrea Callard Papers MSS.156
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Administrative
  - Subseries G: Artist Photographs
    - Fred Krughoof portraits of Andrea Callard. also includes images of Alan Saret. Black and white contact sheets and negatives. Taken post 1976, at Lispenard., undated; cuid22619 (Box 6, Folder 560)
- Series IV: Other Artist Files
  Series IV: Other Artist Files includes individual and group artist files arranged alphabetically. The series is divided into three suseries. Subseries A includes Individual artist files arranged alphabetically by last name. Subseries B includes group projects arranged chronologically. Subseries C includes miscellaneous and unknown materials.
  - Subseries A: Individual artist files
    - ABC NO RIO Cardboard Air Band., undated; cuid22620 (Box 6, Folder 561)
    - Acconci, Vito, undated; cuid22621 (Box 6, Folder 562)
    - Arai, Tomie, undated; cuid22622 (Box 6, Folder 565)
    - Becket, Mack, undated; cuid22623 (Box 6, Folder 566)
    - Bellamy, Peter, undated; cuid22624 (Box 6, Folder 567)
    - Blane, Marc, undated; cuid22625 (Box 6, Folder 568)
    - Brown, Barbara Miller, undated; cuid22626 (Box 6, Folder 569)
    - Caldwell, Catherine [Randi], undated; cuid22627 (Box 6, Folder 570)
    - Callan, Trissy, undated; cuid22628 (Box 6, Folder 581)
    - Cardoso, Maria Fernand, undated; cuid22629 (Box 6, Folder 582)
    - Carpi, Cioni, undated; cuid22630 (Box 6, Folder 583)
    - Chadha, Gurinder, undated; cuid22631 (Box 6, Folder 584)
    - Corber, Mitch, undated; cuid22632 (Box 6, Folder 586)
    - Crowe, Susan Spencer, undated; cuid22633 (Box 6, Folder 587)
    - Dickson, Jane, undated; cuid22634 (Box 6, Folder 588)
    - Ernst, Max, undated; cuid22635 (Box 6, Folder 589)
    - Fend, Peter, undated; cuid22636 (Box 6, Folder 590)
    - Geller, Matthew, undated; cuid22637 (Box 6, Folder 591)
    - Glier, Mike, undated; cuid22638 (Box 6, Folder 592)
    - Haring, Keith, undated; cuid22639 (Box 6, Folder 594)
    - Hodgkin, Howard, undated; cuid22640 (Box 6, Folder 595)
    - Hurbide, Graciela, undated; cuid22641 (Box 6, Folder 598)
    - Jones, Juan, undated; cuid22642 (Box 6, Folder 599)
    - Kahane, Lisa, undated; cuid22643 (Box 6, Folder 600)
    - Kohlhofer, Christof, undated; cuid22644 (Box 6, Folder 601)
    - Korns, Stephen, undated; cuid22645 (Box 6, Folder 602)
    - Krughoff, Fred, undated; cuid22646 (Box 6, Folder 603)
    - Laub, Steven, undated; cuid22647 (Box 6, Folder 604)
    - Lee, Jung Jin, undated; cuid22648 (Box 6, Folder 605)
    - Linder, Alf, undated; cuid22649 (Box 6, Folder 606)
    - Mayer, Rosemary, undated; cuid22650 (Box 6, Folder 607)
    - Mock, Richard Basil. Access copies of New York Times artworks, undated; cuid22651 (Box 6, Folder 608)
    - Naito, Jiro, undated; cuid22652 (Box 6, Folder 612)
    - Nathan, Gail, undated; cuid22653 (Box 6, Folder 613)
    - Nechvatal, Joseph, undated; cuid22654 (Box 6, Folder 615)
    - Nichols, Alice W., undated; cuid22655 (Box 6, Folder 616)
    - Otterness, Tom, undated; cuid22656 (Box 6, Folder 617)
    - Perlman, Cara, undated; cuid22657 (Box 6, Folder 618)
    - Roddy, Mike, undated; cuid22658 (Box 6, Folder 619)
    - Rupp, Christy, undated; cuid22659 (Box 6, Folder 620)
    - Saaar, Alison, undated; cuid22660 (Box 6, Folder 621)
    - Saret, Alan, undated; cuid22661 (Box 6, Folder 622)
    - Seltman, R.L., undated; cuid22662 (Box 6, Folder 623)
    - Schaumburger, Ann, undated; cuid22663 (Box 6, Folder 625)
    - Sidburney, Alex, undated; cuid22664 (Box 6, Folder 626)
    - Smith, Martin, undated; cuid22665 (Box 6, Folder 627)
    - Sussler, Betsy, undated; cuid22666 (Box 6, Folder 628)
    - Takenaga, Barbara, undated; cuid22667 (Box 6, Folder 629)
    - Trapnell, Baylor, undated; cuid22668 (Box 6, Folder 631)
    - Turre, Michele, undated; cuid22669 (Box 6, Folder 632)
    - Viner, Frank Lincoln, undated; cuid22670 (Box 6, Folder 633)
    - Warren, Tom, undated; cuid22671 (Box 6, Folder 634)
    - Waters, Jonathan, undated; cuid22672 (Box 6, Folder 635)
    - Weitzman, Lee, undated; cuid22673 (Box 6, Folder 636)
    - Williams, Reese, undated; cuid22674 (Box 6, Folder 638)
    - Williamson, Philemona, undated; cuid22675 (Box 6, Folder 639)
    - Winters, Robin, undated; cuid22676 (Box 6, Folder 640)
    - Wirsum, Karl, undated; cuid22677 (Box 6, Folder 641)
    - Youngblood, Daisy, undated; cuid22678 (Box 6, Folder 642)
  - Subseries B: Collaborations and Group Shows
    - AICA invitation, undated; cuid22679 (Box 6, Folder 643)
    - "Life Mixing" includes Reese Williams, Theresa Cha, Maxine Borenstein, Ed Harker and Brian Mealins, 1975; cuid22680 (Box 6, Folder 645)
    - "Practical Esthetic Services" business card. Includes Fend, Fitzgibbon, Holzer, Nadin, Prince and Winters., undated; cuid22681 (Box 6, Folder 646)
    - Miscellaneous collaborations and group shows., undated; cuid22682 (Box 6, Folder 648)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous and Unknown Artists
    - Graffitti style drawing, undated; cuid22683 (Box 6, Folder 649)
    - Color photographs of Cara Perlman, ca. 1978; cuid22684 (Box 6, Folder 651)
    - Miscellaneous images on white paper, undated; cuid22685 (Box 6, Folder 652)
    - Faux advertisements with type and circles, undated; cuid22686 (Box 6, Folder 657)
    - Black and white negatives, Fashion Moda, Corona park, undated; cuid22687 (Box 6, Folder 659)
    - Black and white negatives, White Columns, 1981; cuid22688 (Box 6, Folder 661)
- Series V: Correspondence
  Series V: Correspondence includes Andrea Callard's personal and administrative correspondence organized alphabetically by sender. The series is divided into four subseries. Subseries A contains correspondence from senders with known first and last names arranged alphabetically by last name. Subseries B includes correspondence from senders with known first names or first initials organized alphbetically. Subseries C contains correspondence from Andrea callard organized alphabetically by addressee. Subseries D includes unlabeld or illegible correspondence.
  - Subseries A: Last name, First name
    - Amdur, Latifa, undated; cuid22689 (Box 6, Folder 663)
    - Antenen, Susan, undated; cuid22690 (Box 6, Folder 664)
    - Art In America, undated; cuid22691 (Box 6, Folder 665)
    - Artists Space, undated; cuid22692 (Box 6, Folder 666)
    - Artlink Artspace, undated; cuid22693 (Box 6, Folder 667)
    - Atcher, R.W., undated; cuid22694 (Box 6, Folder 668)
    - Becket, Mac, undated; cuid22695 (Box 6, Folder 669)
    - Bellamy, Peter, undated; cuid22696 (Box 6, Folder 670)
    - Binder, Laurie, undated; cuid22697 (Box 6, Folder 671)
    - Blanchet, Jo, undated; cuid22698 (Box 6, Folder 672)
    - Brown, Duncan, undated; cuid22699 (Box 6, Folder 673)
    - Brown, Gary, undated; cuid22700 (Box 6, Folder 674)
    - Burns, Mark [Tribeca-SoHo Animal Hospital], undated; cuid22701 (Box 6, Folder 675)
    - Callard, Mrs. C.G. [Gram], undated; cuid22702 (Box 6, Folder 676)
    - Callard, C.G. [Gramp], undated; cuid22703 (Box 6, Folder 677)
    - Callard, Roberta [sister], undated; cuid22704 (Box 6, Folder 678)
    - Cha, Theresa, undated; cuid22705 (Box 6, Folder 679)
    - Chaplin, Ed, undated; cuid22706 (Box 6, Folder 680)
    - Cohen, Marjorie, undated; cuid22707 (Box 6, Folder 681)
    - Cooper, Ellen, undated; cuid22708 (Box 6, Folder 682)
    - Corber, Anne, undated; cuid22709 (Box 6, Folder 683)
    - Coualt, A., undated; cuid22710 (Box 6, Folder 684)
    - Davis, Susan, undated; cuid22711 (Box 6, Folder 685)
    - Dean, Kentley Benson, undated; cuid22712 (Box 6, Folder 686)
    - Denny, Robert, undated; cuid22713 (Box 6, Folder 687)
    - Dixon, Jo, undated; cuid22714 (Box 6, Folder 688)
    - Douksza, John, undated; cuid22715 (Box 6, Folder 689)
    - Fend, Peter, undated; cuid22716 (Box 6, Folder 690)
    - Fridley, Joanne, undated; cuid22717 (Box 6, Folder 691)
    - Garvin, Mary, undated; cuid22718 (Box 6, Folder 692)
    - Geller, Matthew, undated; cuid22719 (Box 6, Folder 693)
    - Greenwood, Martha, undated; cuid22720 (Box 6, Folder 694)
    - Haggerty, Beth, undated; cuid22721 (Box 6, Folder 695)
    - Haskes, undated; cuid22722 (Box 6, Folder 696)
    - Heavenrich, Ned, undated; cuid22723 (Box 6, Folder 697)
    - Heyward, Julia, undated; cuid22724 (Box 6, Folder 698)
    - Howland, Rebecca, undated; cuid22725 (Box 6, Folder 699)
    - Hughes, Danne, undated; cuid22726 (Box 6, Folder 700)
    - Hughes, Robert, undated; cuid22727 (Box 6, Folder 701)
    - Huttinger, Peter, undated; cuid22728 (Box 6, Folder 702)
    - Jacobs, Joyce Ringle, undated; cuid22729 (Box 6, Folder 703)
    - Johnson, Trishia, undated; cuid22730 (Box 6, Folder 704)
    - Kammer, Prexy, undated; cuid22731 (Box 6, Folder 705)
    - Keeton, Darra, undated; cuid22732 (Box 6, Folder 706)
    - Kladzyle, Pam, undated; cuid22733 (Box 6, Folder 707)
    - Klein, Ann, undated; cuid22734 (Box 6, Folder 708)
    - Klein, Harriette, undated; cuid22735 (Box 6, Folder 709)
    - Knox, Dede, undated; cuid22736 (Box 6, Folder 710)
    - Krughoff, Fred, undated; cuid22737 (Box 6, Folder 711)
    - Leune, Caidyl, undated; cuid22738 (Box 6, Folder 712)
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, undated; cuid22739 (Box 6, Folder 713)
    - McMahon, Jeff, undated; cuid22740 (Box 6, Folder 714)
    - Martin, Patty [Mrs. Hartschorn], undated; cuid22741 (Box 6, Folder 715)
    - Matusak, Zack, undated; cuid22742 (Box 6, Folder 716)
    - Mayer, Rosemary, undated; cuid22743 (Box 6, Folder 717)
    - Messner and Moenig, undated; cuid22744 (Box 6, Folder 718)
    - Messner, Ann, undated; cuid22745 (Box 6, Folder 719)
    - Miller, Barb, undated; cuid22746 (Box 6, Folder 720)
    - Mock, Richard and Patti, undated; cuid22747 (Box 6, Folder 721)
    - Mullin, Molly, undated; cuid22748 (Box 6, Folder 722)
    - Nathan, Gail, undated; cuid22749 (Box 6, Folder 723)
    - Nichols, Dr. Alice, undated; cuid22750 (Box 6, Folder 724)
    - Nolan, Janet, undated; cuid22751 (Box 6, Folder 725)
    - O'Neill, Bonnie, undated; cuid22752 (Box 6, Folder 726)
    - Passera, Bill, undated; cuid22753 (Box 6, Folder 727)
    - Payne, Sandra, undated; cuid22754 (Box 6, Folder 728)
    - Peckman, Glen, undated; cuid22755 (Box 6, Folder 729)
    - Perlman, Cara, undated; cuid22756 (Box 6, Folder 730)
    - Petior, Anna, undated; cuid22757 (Box 6, Folder 731)
    - Potter, Janet, undated; cuid22758 (Box 6, Folder 732)
    - Provincial Museum at Hasselt, undated; cuid22759 (Box 6, Folder 733)
    - Rees, Sarah, undated; cuid22760 (Box 6, Folder 734)
    - Reynolds, Jock, undated; cuid22761 (Box 6, Folder 735)
    - Romeu, Joost, undated; cuid22762 (Box 6, Folder 736)
    - Rubin, Bernice, undated; cuid22763 (Box 6, Folder 737)
    - Rupp, Christy, undated; cuid22764 (Box 6, Folder 738)
    - Roddy, D.S., undated; cuid22765 (Box 6, Folder 739)
    - Saret, Alan, undated; cuid22766 (Box 6, Folder 740)
    - Segerr, Nan, undated; cuid22767 (Box 6, Folder 741)
    - Seltman, Robert L., undated; cuid22768 (Box 7, Folder 742)
    - Siegle, Susan, undated; cuid22769 (Box 7, Folder 743)
    - Slotkin, Terry, undated; cuid22770 (Box 7, Folder 744)
    - Smagula, Howard, undated; cuid22771 (Box 7, Folder 745)
    - Smith, Bob, undated; cuid22772 (Box 7, Folder 746)
    - Smith, Susan, undated; cuid22773 (Box 7, Folder 747)
    - Snyder, Molly, undated; cuid22774 (Box 7, Folder 748)
    - Staten, Pat, undated; cuid22775 (Box 7, Folder 749)
    - Stevens, May, undated; cuid22776 (Box 7, Folder 750)
    - Stoltz, Susan, undated; cuid22777 (Box 7, Folder 751)
    - Trapnell, Baylor, undated; cuid22778 (Box 7, Folder 752)
    - Vincent, Jim, undated; cuid22779 (Box 7, Folder 753)
    - Vincent, Kitty, undated; cuid22780 (Box 7, Folder 754)
    - Vukos, Jim, undated; cuid22781 (Box 7, Folder 755)
    - Ward, B., undated; cuid22782 (Box 7, Folder 756)
    - Wellman, Jerry, undated; cuid22783 (Box 7, Folder 757)
    - Wilde, Betty [Bronx River Restoration], undated; cuid22784 (Box 7, Folder 758)
    - Williams, Carol [also known as Winefred and Carol Gordon], undated; cuid22785 (Box 7, Folder 759)
    - Williams, Reese, undated; cuid22786 (Box 7, Folder 760)
    - Wilson, Martha Redy Story, undated; cuid22787 (Box 7, Folder 761)
    - Winkleman, Harriet, undated; cuid22788 (Box 7, Folder 762)
    - Wolff, Whitney, undated; cuid22789 (Box 7, Folder 763)
    - Wornsy, Al, undated; cuid22790 (Box 7, Folder 764)
    - Youngblood, Daisy, undated; cuid22791 (Box 7, Folder 765)
  - Subseries B: First name
    - Allen, undated; cuid22792 (Box 7, Folder 766)
    - Ann, undated; cuid22793 (Box 7, Folder 767)
    - Beckie, undated; cuid22794 (Box 7, Folder 768)
    - Bill, undated; cuid22795 (Box 7, Folder 769)
    - Carrina, undated; cuid22796 (Box 7, Folder 770)
    - Chris, undated; cuid22797 (Box 7, Folder 771)
    - Clarissa, undated; cuid22798 (Box 7, Folder 772)
    - Dennis, undated; cuid22799 (Box 7, Folder 773)
    - E.W.H., undated; cuid22800 (Box 7, Folder 774)
    - Harriet Z., undated; cuid22801 (Box 7, Folder 775)
    - Irene, undated; cuid22802 (Box 7, Folder 776)
    - Jane, undated; cuid22803 (Box 7, Folder 777)
    - Jean [aunt], undated; cuid22804 (Box 7, Folder 778)
    - Josh, undated; cuid22805 (Box 7, Folder 779)
    - Kris and Char, undated; cuid22806 (Box 7, Folder 780)
    - Laura, undated; cuid22807 (Box 7, Folder 781)
    - Larry, undated; cuid22808 (Box 7, Folder 782)
    - Liana, Zara and Jon, undated; cuid22809 (Box 7, Folder 783)
    - Marietta, undated; cuid22810 (Box 7, Folder 784)
    - Mark, undated; cuid22811 (Box 7, Folder 785)
    - MEB, undated; cuid22812 (Box 7, Folder 786)
    - Meg, undated; cuid22813 (Box 7, Folder 787)
    - Mindy, undated; cuid22814 (Box 7, Folder 788)
    - Mother, undated; cuid22815 (Box 7, Folder 789)
    - Nancy, undated; cuid22816 (Box 7, Folder 790)
    - Otis B., undated; cuid22817 (Box 7, Folder 791)
    - Pam, undated; cuid22818 (Box 7, Folder 792)
    - Pamela, undated; cuid22819 (Box 7, Folder 793)
    - Pat, undated; cuid22820 (Box 7, Folder 794)
    - Ralph, undated; cuid22821 (Box 7, Folder 795)
    - Randi and Mark, undated; cuid22822 (Box 7, Folder 796)
    - Red, undated; cuid22823 (Box 7, Folder 797)
    - Rose, undated; cuid22824 (Box 7, Folder 798)
    - Ruby, undated; cuid22825 (Box 7, Folder 799)
    - Ruth, undated; cuid22826 (Box 7, Folder 800)
    - Ruth C., undated; cuid22827 (Box 7, Folder 801)
    - Scott, undated; cuid22828 (Box 7, Folder 802)
    - Sheila, undated; cuid22829 (Box 7, Folder 803)
    - Sophie, undated; cuid22830 (Box 7, Folder 804)
    - Susan, undated; cuid22831 (Box 7, Folder 805)
    - Suzanne, undated; cuid22832 (Box 7, Folder 806)
    - T., undated; cuid22833 (Box 7, Folder 807)
    - T.B., undated; cuid22834 (Box 7, Folder 808)
  - Subseries C: From Andrea Callard
    - Dad, undated; cuid22835 (Box 7, Folder 809)
    - James, undated; cuid22836 (Box 7, Folder 810)
    - Joe and Claudio, undated; cuid22837 (Box 7, Folder 811)
    - Joost Romeu, undated; cuid22838 (Box 7, Folder 812)
    - Pat, undated; cuid22839 (Box 7, Folder 813)
    - Kitty and Jim Pearson Vincent, undated; cuid22840 (Box 7, Folder 814)
    - Reese and Carol Williams, undated; cuid22841 (Box 7, Folder 815)
    - Reese Williams, undated; cuid22842 (Box 7, Folder 816)
    - unknown, undated; cuid22843 (Box 7, Folder 817)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous
    - Addresses and contact information, undated; cuid22844 (Box 7, Folder 818)
    - Unlabeled or illegible correspondence, undated; cuid22845 (Box 7, Folder 819)
    - Miscellaneous mail from businesses, undated; cuid22846 (Box 7, Folder 820)
    - Correspondence from others to others [i.e. from Reese Williams to Mark, undated; cuid22847 (Box 7, Folder 821)
- Series VI: Biographical
  This series contains materials related to Andrea Callard's childhood, personal photographs and snapshots as well as personal reflective writing such as dream journals. Materials are arranged in chronological order with undated materials at the end of the series.
  - Membership cards, 1966-1979; cuid22848 (Box 7, Folder 822)
  - Photograph of Andrea Callard's house at Cranbrook, 1966-1968; cuid22849 (Box 7, Folder 823)
  - Citizenship Award from Kingswood School Cranbrook student council, 1968; cuid22850 (Box 7, Folder 824)
  - Indianapolis 500 ticket, 1974; cuid22851 (Box 7, Folder 825)
  - Callard photograph of Robin Winters, Laurie Binder, Baylor Trapnell on vacation together in Maine, 1974; cuid22852 (Box 7, Folder 826)
  - Personal Notes to self, 1974-1978; cuid22853 (Box 7, Folder 827)
  - Dreams, 1974-1975; cuid22854 (Box 7, Folder 828)
  - Dreams, Plans and other notes, 1975; cuid22855 (Box 7, Folder 829)
  - Miscellaneous writing, 1975; cuid22856 (Box 7, Folder 830)
  - letter information occurence, 1975; cuid22857 (Box 7, Folder 831)
  - Materials removed from Distance Fool by Gary Brown, 1975; cuid22858 (Box 7, Folder 832)
  - McBarney YMCA yoga class, 1976; cuid22859 (Box 7, Folder 833)
  - Candid color snapshots, Andrea Callard, Fred Krughoff, the Vincents, and the Williams, 1979; cuid22860 (Box 7, Folder 834)
  - Andrea Callard and Matthew Geller in the Berkshires, 26 color slides, 1982; cuid22861 (Box 7, Folder 835)
  - Color slides, sailing school, 12 color slides, 1982; cuid22862 (Box 7, Folder 836)
  - Cherry Valley Sulivan County House, rented with Gail Nathan. Color slides. 56 color slides, 1982; cuid22863 (Box 7, Folder 837)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, unlabeled and ungrouped. Mostly snapshots, undated; cuid22864 (Box 7, Folder 838)
  - Kingswood School Cranbrook alumni magazine. Andrea Callard wrote the section for her year, undated; cuid22865 (Box 7, Folder 839)
  - Color snapshots. Wait staff at Claudios at the beach, undated; cuid22866 (Box 7, Folder 840)
  - Word Debris [not fun], undated; cuid22867 (Box 7, Folder 841)
  - Lists of books to read, undated; cuid22868 (Box 7, Folder 842)
  - Souvenir slides from Galerie du Jeu Paume, undated; cuid22869 (Box 7, Folder 843)
  - Acupuncture, undated; cuid22870 (Box 7, Folder 845)
  - Healing, undated; cuid22871 (Box 7, Folder 846)
  - Thoughts on Relationship with Fred, undated; cuid22872 (Box 7, Folder 847)
  - Miscellaneous color snapshots, stacked together. Includes some of Ailanthus trees or Cynthia larvae., undated; cuid22873 (Binder J, Folder a)
  - Baylor Trapnell cuts up safe at 150 Chambers St., undated; cuid22874 (Binder J, Folder b)
  - Color snapshots. Includes images of Ned Heavenrich in California, Postcards from Reese and Carol Williams, Lispenard Renovation, AC and others on Staten Island Ferry, Brick City dog, Brick City and Megan. Post 1976, undated; cuid22875 (Binder J, Folder c)
  - Color snapshots. Images of the views from 40 Lispenard St, Canal St Post office. Post-1976, undated; cuid22876 (Binder J, Folder d)
  - Color snapshots. Images of the view of Lispenard St, gamblers enroute to Atlantic City, undated; cuid22877 (Binder J, Folder e)
  - Color snapshots. Images of the views from PS1, Andrea Callard and Cara Perlman at PS1, undated; cuid22878 (Binder J, Folder f)
  - Color snapshots. Images of Brooklyn Bridge, tree, Queens from PS1 and Forsythia near NY Botanic Garden., undated; cuid22879 (Binder J, Folder g)
  - Color snapshots. Images and negatives of New York City., undated; cuid22880 (Binder J, Folder h)
  - Color snapshots. Images of Ailanthus in NYC and editing room in studio at 40 Lispenard., undated; cuid22881 (Binder J, Folder i)
  - Color snapshots. "Jim and Kathy Vincent lived in my Tent Sculpture while in NY to edit film about fishin in Costa Rica", undated; cuid22882 (Binder J, Folder j)
  - Color snapshots. Corinne and studio set of 11-12 film and Fred Krughoff in Florida, undated; cuid22883 (Binder J, Folder k)
  - Lispenard Renovation, undated; cuid22884 (Binder J, Folder l)
  - Color snapshots. Images of Mac Becket, Girl "plumber", Manhattan Bridge, Ed Harker, Grandmother reading Times., undated; cuid22885 (Binder J, Folder m)
- Series VII: Printed Materials
  This series includes printed materials. Items are arrnaged in alphabetical order by author's last name.
  - Associated Press Stylebook, 1970; cuid22886 (Box 7, Folder 849)
  - Avalanche Magazine promotional callendar, 1974; cuid22887 (Box 7, Folder 850)
  - Brownsmead flier, undated; cuid22888 (Box 7, Folder 851)
  - Bu Gao Ban, Chinatown History Project Newsletter, 1986; cuid22889 (Box 7, Folder 851A)
  - Callard, Madden and Associates: Corporate Financial Performances and Stock Prices, undated; cuid22890 (Box 7, Folder 852)
  - A Citizen's Guide to Adirondack Park Agency Land Use Regulations, 1980; cuid22891 (Box 7, Folder 853)
  - Everglades informational brochure, undated; cuid22892 (Box 7, Folder 854)
  - Gedulo, Harry. Film Makers on Film Making., 1973; cuid22893 (Box 7, Folder 856)
  - Geller, Suzanne. The Artist's Craft, 1981; cuid22894 (Box 7, Folder 857)
  - Gersten, Robert. The Spirit of Ole Bryant Lake, 2000; cuid22895 (Box 7, Folder 858)
  - Goldman, David. A is for OX, cuid22896 (Box 7, Folder 859)
  - Halprin, Lawrence. The RSVP Cycles., 1969; cuid22897 (Box 7, Folder 860)
  - Just Another Asshole #6, 1983; cuid22898 (Box 8, Folder 861)
  - Key West Aloe Fragrance and Cosmetics, undated; cuid22899 (Box 8, Folder 862)
  - Klayman, Toby Judith. The Artists' Survival Manual, 1984; cuid22900 (Box 8, Folder 863)
  - Lippard, Lucy. Get the Message?, 1984; cuid22901 (Box 8, Folder 864)
  - Malone NY, 1985; cuid22902 (Box 8, Folder 864A)
  - National African American Museum Project, Imagining Families: Images and Voices, 1994-1995; cuid22903 (Box 8, Folder 865)
  - National Inspirer, 1973; cuid22904 (Box 8, Folder 866)
  - New York Public Library booklists and materials, undated; cuid22905 (Box 8, Folder 867)
  - Official Rental Directory of Accredited Canoe liveries and outfitters, 1980; cuid22906 (Box 8, Folder 868)
  - Porter Cable Router instruction manual, undated; cuid22907 (Box 8, Folder 869)
  - Postcard images, undated; cuid22908 (Box 8, Folder 870)
  - Printed Matter, Inc. catalogue, undated; cuid22909 (Box 8, Folder 871)
  - Public Art Fund Newsletter, 1984; cuid22910 (Box 8, Folder 872)
  - Real Life Magazine, 1991; cuid22911 (Box 8, Folder 873)
  - Smith, Mabel Parker. Greene County, New York: A Short History., undated; cuid22912 (Box 8, Folder 875)
  - Taking Over? A Guide to eleven non-native plants that are pests in Wave Hill's woods, 1982; cuid22913 (Box 8, Folder 876)
  - Tanam Press Catalogue, undated; cuid22914 (Box 8, Folder 877)
  - Thoreau, Henry David. Ktaadn, 1980; cuid22915 (Box 8, Folder 878)
  - Tourism Pamphlets, undated; cuid22916 (Box 8, Folder 879)
  - Turning Leaves: The Family Albums of Two Japanese American Families, 1989; cuid22917 (Box 8, Folder 880)
  - USA Plant Visits 1977-1978, undated; cuid22918 (Box 8, Folder 881)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, undated; cuid22919 (Box 8, Folder 882)
- Series VIII: Artifacts
  This series includes objects and artifacts.
  - Red Feathered pill-box hat. Used in Red Anger polaroids, undated; cuid22920 (Box 10)
  - Starched fabric wallet, east asian style design. In plastic packaging., undated; cuid22921 (Box 10)
  - Kodak Super 8mm film canister, empty, undated; cuid22922 (Box 10)
  - Ziplock bag containing film editing materials including Fuji Film splicing Tape 100, Bilora Tape-rolls, two empty film cores and canisters, two envelopse of super eight slipce tapes and a baggie containing splice fragments., undated; cuid22923 (Box 10)
  - Mirror, black letter "A" used in "A Dressing Wall" images and "Red Anger Association"., undated; cuid22924 (Box 11)
  - White "A" on mirror. Used in "A Dressing Wall", cuid22925 (Box 11)
- Series IX: Video recordings
  Video materials consist of production elements for media works by Callard and documentation of works by others. Access copies may not be available yet. Please check with the Fales Archivist.